electro-tech-online.com 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy - WTWH Media LLC

WTWH Media, LLC (“WTWH”, “we”, or “us”) is committed to ensuring the privacy of our users. The following is our privacy policy and we hope it clarifies how WTWH processes and uses certain information collected via our network of websites. A listing of WTWH online properties can be found at wtwhmedia.com and links to this privacy policy are found on every website. By using our Sites, you consent to the terms of this Policy.

### Information collection when you visit our network of sites

Some information is automatically collected, such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system, browser type and the time and date of your visit. This information is collected through the use of “cookies”. Cookies are small files that are stored on your web browser to give you a unique but anonymous identification. Certain cookies we use on WTWH websites do collect personal data as defined by the GDPR when combined with other services. And by personal data, this is typically limited to location and possibly IP address. WTWH does not collect any genetic or biometric data.

We also use cookies on our Sites to keep track of services you have used, to record registration information regarding your login name and password, to ensure you do not repeatedly see advertisements, to record your user preferences and to keep you logged into the sites.

Additionally, we use, and allow third parties to use, various Web technologies on the sites to monitor the effectiveness of advertising or for other legitimate purposes.

We use third parties such as ad servers or network advertisers, to deliver ads to you on our behalf. These third-party ad servers may use cookies or other technology to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our sites in order to use it to present advertisements that may be of interest to you. We understand under the GDPR that these cookies are more than functional cookies and users have a choice of using while on websites.

### Data Controllers & Security

WTWH can be considered a data controller and processor under the GDPR and as a cloud based company we rely on 3rd parties to process and control data on our behalf. WTWH has chosen vendors that are GDPR compliant and provide the highest standards in data safeguarding, storage and transmission. WTWH designed its platforms and services with built-in data security and privacy services, platform and tools needed to help safeguard sensitive data wherever it resides. WTWH Media implements appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure a level of security appropriate to the risk.

The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) takes effect on January 1st, 2020. This new privacy law requires businesses to disclose how they treat consumers’ personal information if they process information on individuals residing in the state of California. WTWH Media is exempt from the CCPA Act, but adheres to individual requests for information and data removal. WTWH Media also acts as a data processor or ‘service provider’ and the CCPA does not apply to service providers.

### How we use the information

We use personal data to process your requests or transactions, provide you with products and services, and inform you about other products or services we think will be of interest. Certain registration information on premium content is shared with our business partners. For example some access to WTWH or other vendors data / content requires secure user registration to download or access information. Also, we use the information we collect to:

  * contact you for administrative purposes or provide you with customer service
  * complete transactions requested by you
  * respond to any questions, problems or complaints, or request feedback
  * organize Sites and various services and activities to better serve you and customize or develop our products and services
  * send you emails or other communications containing information about products and services that you have requested

Personal data provided on our sites may be linked together or merged with other personal data we obtain about you so that we may better understand your needs and inform you about our products or services and those of our business partners. In addition, if we receive personal data from third parties with whom we have business relationships, we may combine this information with the other personal data we maintain about you. In either case, this Policy governs this information.

### Disclosure of Information

We share personal information with third-party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. These functions may include, for example, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and processing payment transactions. In all cases we limit the information shared with our third-party vendors to that which is necessary to carry out those functions.

We also disclose personal data when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply this Policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our users’ rights, property or safety; to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, our Site; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.

In addition, information about our users, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing or sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of our business assets.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our sites contain links to other Web sites. Links from our sites to other sites or content are provided for your convenience only, and we do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties or other sites. Any personal data you provide on linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information. In the case of a link to a WTWH Media site, this privacy policy is applicable.

### CAN-SPAM

WTWH adheres rigorously to all [CAN-SPAM](https://www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business-center/guidance/can-spam-act-compliance-guide-business) legislation and we always make it easy for opt-in recipients to opt-out of any communication sent on behalf of WTWH Media. We utilize 3rd party data processors in our emailing campaigns and those parties have been chosen for their adherence to the same CAN-SPAM legislation and data integrity, safety and security. GDPR requires the easy ‘forgetting’ or deletion of user data and WTWH adheres to accommodating these requests. Due to ensuring those users who globally opt-out of email delivery, a unique identifier – an email only in this case – is still stored with our 3rd party processors to ensure that email as an identifier is not added back into our databases.  A user can be added back into our system only if they specifically double opt in via our secure forms to validate the email as owned or authorized by them and then agree to receive communications. All other data associated with a request for deletion will be eliminated from any WTWH system or database.

### Updates

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.

### Dedicated Contact for Privacy Matters and Data Protection

Please contact Marshall Matheson – Tel +1.888.543.2447 and/or use the form on this page.

The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on December 20, 2019
